{
    "id": "9b5843b8cd6a41e4a743fc8af2a47e1c",
    "title": "Simple present tense worksheet",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "8d015bbf6cfe45419445de7e83d12dee",
            "title": "Simple Present Tense Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "....................... you know his name?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Do",
                        "Does",
                        "Has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We ..................... . strangers.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do not trust",
                        "does not trust",
                        "have not trust"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Arun .....................… with his left hand.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "write",
                        "writes",
                        "writing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Salim ..................... for the national hockey team.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "play",
                        "plays",
                        "playing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "My parents ....................... me to get good grades.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "want",
                        "wants",
                        "wanting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where ...................... you live?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "does",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "What ………………. he do?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "does",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Rahul ………………….. not have a job.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "does",
                        "do",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Shiva ..................... . an apartment in the city.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "own",
                        "owns",
                        "owning"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Gauri ....................... lovely long hair.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "has",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}